Waris Khan

Kolhapur, Maharashtra, India



waris ck@yahoo.com



9689786033



linkedin.com/in/waris-khan-5784ab21

Summary

Being a Professional, keen interest in making career in a sales and marketing field to give full potential efforts to the organization which provide me an opportunity to learn and grow with the organization.

I plan to execute this with my dedication and sincerity to achieve great success of the organization with my highest potential.

Sales and Distribution professional with total experience of 16 years in the industry.

- Sales Management
- Sales Operations
- Key Account Management
- Market Research
- Expertise in Distribution
- Channel Partner Appointment
- Team Handling
- Strategize and Planing to Achieve Company Goals
- Quick Learner
- Trainer
- Monitor Marketing activities

Experience



Mobile Accessorises Zonal Sales Manager

Azelo Dpower Private Limited

Aug 2019 - Oct 2020 (1 year 3 months)

Profile & Responsibilities:

- Achieve Revenue Target for Zone.
- Appoint New Channel Partners & Recruitment of Sales Team.
- Co-ordination with Business Correspondence.
- Motivate & Encourage the Sales Team.
- · Coordinating with Team (Multiple Super stockist, Multiple Team members and Multiple Distributors).
- · Coordinating & Settlement of claims of channel partners.



Zonal Sales Manager

Wise Apps Pvt. Ltd

Jan 2016 - Oct 2017 (1 year 10 months)

Profile & Responsibilities:

Achieve Revenue & Insurance Target

Appoint New Channel Partners & Recruitment of Sales Team.

Co-ordination with Business Correspondence

Motivate & Encourage the Sales Team.

Coordinating with Team (8 team members and 2 Distributors).

Coordinating & Settlement of claims of channel partner

Sales Manager

First Rand Bank

Dec 2013 - Dec 2014 (1 year 1 month)

Profile & Responsibilities:

Achieve Account opening, Revenue & Insurance Target

Appoint New Channel Partners & Recruitment of Sales Team.

Co-ordination with Business Correspondence

Motivate & Encourage the Sales Team.

Allocation of poster and event supporter...

Coordinating with Team (3 team members and 4 business correspondence and 18 promoters).

Coordinating & Settlement of claims of channel partners.

Assistant Manager

Loop Mobile India (P) Ltd

Nov 2010 - Dec 2013 (3 years 2 months)

Profile & Responsibilities:

- · Achieve Activation, Revenue & Unbarring Targets.
- Appoint New Channel Partners & Recruitment of Sales Team.
- Co-ordination with Channel Partners.
- Motivate & Encourage the Sales Team.
- Allocation of poster and event supporter.
- Tracking competition data.
- Coordinating with Prepaid Team (16 team members and 2 Distributors).
- · Coordinating & Settlement of claims of channel partners.
- Compiling required data as and when required by company.
- Coordination with Sales team for all details required by company.
- Data related to sales and marketing.

Senior Executive

Etisalat DB Telecom Pvt. Ltd.

Oct 2009 - Oct 2010 (1 year 1 month)

Profile & Responsibilities:

- · Distributors profiling
- Collection of letter of interest from the distributors.
- Retail mapping
- · Association with 8 distributors for the company.
- Etisalat franchise allocation.
- PD (premium dealer) mapping.
- Analysis of know your area.
- Building Brand image & Product awareness in the market.
- · Handling MRO town (Kurndwad).

Additional Responsibilities

- · Handled 4 months operational responsibility in Mumbai for Sales
- · Establishing & organizing the distributors for sales activities
- Successfully launched company's product "cheers" in Mumbai market
- Taking Additional responsibilities of MRO town.

Assistant Manager

Idea Cellular Ltd

Jul 2008 - Sep 2009 (1 year 3 months)

Profile & Responsibilities:

- · Achieving unbarring, Revenue & T n C Targets.
- Appointing distributors & Recruitment of Sales Team.
- Co-ordination with Channel Partners for LUT sites.
- · Motivating & Encouraging the Sales Team.
- Tracking competition data.
- Coordinating with Prepaid Team (7 team members and 5 Distributors).
- Allocation of budget & Settlement of claims.
- Providing required data on a regular basis.

Territory Sales Manager

BPL Mobile Communications Ltd.

Feb 2007 - Jul 2008 (1 year 6 months)

Profile & Responsibilities:

- · Achieve Activation, Revenue & Unbarring Targets.
- Appoint New Channel Partners & Recruitment of Sales Team.
- · Co-ordination with Channel Partners.
- Motivate & Encourage the Sales Team.
- Allocation of poster and event supporter.
- Tracking competition data.
- Coordinating with Prepaid Team (16 team members and 2 Distributors).
- Coordinating & Settlement of claims of channel partners.
- Compiling required data as and when required by company.
- Coordination with Sales team for all details required by company.
- Data related to sales and marketing.

TSI Pre Paid Sales.

Hutchison Essar Cellular Ltd.

Mar 2003 - Feb 2007 (4 years)

Profile & Responsibilities:

- Achieve Activation, Revenue & Unbarring Targets.
- Appoint New Channel Partners & Recruitment of Sales Team.
- · Co-ordination with Channel Partners.
- Motivate & Encourage the Sales Team.
- Allocation of poster and event supporter.
- Tracking competition data.
- Coordinating with Prepaid Team (11 team members and 3 Distributors).
- Coordinating & Settlement of claims of channel partners.
- Compiling required data as and when required by company.

- Coordination with Sales team for all details required by company.
- · Data related to sales and marketing.

Education



Shivaji University

DBM, Commerce 1997 - 2004



S.M. Lohiya High School and Juniour Collage

12th Class. High School, Commerce 1989 - 1997

Skills

Microsoft Office • Microsoft Excel • Microsoft Word • Customer Service • PowerPoint • English • Windows • Research • Outlook • Public Speaking